so I got a birthday coming up you know
what every time I have a birthday it
kind of amazes me so I was pretty wild
when I was younger and uh I never
thought I was going to live this long
[Music]
surprise wish I known I was going to
live this long I would have saved some
money yeah who knew who
knew of course weirdly enough I'm
finding there are certain benefits to
being broke you know like that whole
economic downturn thing we went through
uh didn't really affect me at
all I'm like what's all the
Hol I think I lost like
$9 that's
not but then you see these people being
interviewed on the news going I lost
$800,000 I'm like well that's what you
get for having so much
money these are hot dogs and these are
ramen
[Music]
noodles enjoy your stew sir enjoy your
stew
cuz rich people don't know anything
about Ramen like Ramen noodles what are
they uh they're 10 for a
dollar that's all you really know sir
they 10 for a buck and you get a whole
weeks with the sodium in every
serving that's some hard py nutrition
for a dime
sir and I may live a long time I have a
lot of longevity in my family all my
grandparents made into their their late
'90s my dad's folks were married made it
75 years they were married 75th
Anniversary yeah weird thing is last
couple years I couldn't even tell them
apart
anymore oh man that's how long they
lived they looked exactly the
same I mean you can tell my grandfather
eventually cuz he'd always tell you the
same thing you know something your
grandmother looks the same now as she
did the day I met her
she must have been a brutal looking
[Applause]
18-year-old obviously she was the one
buying the
beer and my dad my dad has a friend him
and his wife have been married 60 years
60 years and they're going through a
divorce yeah I'm like come on how do you
make it through 60 years of marriage and
finally go that's it I'm out of
here match.com here I
come getting
stupider like you ever done done this
ever vacuum the house and run over a
paper clip or a bobby pin or something
like that about a thousand
times and the machine won't pick it up
and you're and you won't bend over pick
it up and just throw it away you like
bend over pick it up and try in a
different spot there you
go I don't know who you think you're
dealing with up here I got a college
education there it is I win
H $186 that's what it cost to have taken
out of the
motor hey sometimes you got to pay for
your principles you
[Music]
know it's like a washer egg somebody
brought from the house doesn't
[Music]
it so did see my
family over Christmas last year because
of Co and you know honestly it was just
as well cuz my brothers are still giving
me a hard time about my Christmas gift
selection from the year before cuz
there's six kids in my family and
everybody's married and has children so
just like 30 people I have to buy gifts
for so that year I tried something
different and I did all my shopping over
at Dollar General
oh you should see how much you can buy
at that store for
$300 I had to make two trips with a car
that's how much I bought it was
unreal man I walked into my Mom and
Dad's on Christmas morning I got trash
bags full of presents and I'm like I got
gifts per
person then my brother starts open up
his stuff and he's like a th Mini staes
you're an
idiot I don't even have a Min stapler
I'm like dude open up the blue
box got your cover
bro yeah go grow up in a big family go
something old anybody big familyes five
six seven eight kids you he doesn't seem
very happy about it man he's had his arm
crossed the whole time yeah go ahead and
crack your jokes buddy but I'm not there
was a little smile there cuz I bought
cuz he's got his pink tennis shoes on so
pink tennis shoes when his beard I'm an
outdoorsy guy but I can adjust other
situations as well